<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts @ ThatIs.BS</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Posts @ ThatIs.BS</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building in Public</title>
      <link>/post/build-in-public/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/build-in-public/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a post for anyone interested in following along with what I have been&#xA;doing. This has been pinging around in the my head as a necessary update to&#xA;family for months. Sorry about going off the radar, and here is an update on&#xA;what I have been up to and where I&amp;rsquo;m going.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most of 2024 has been a disaster. Earlier in the year I built excitement for a&#xA;business idea for a sports cards market place. The idea is that no current&#xA;market exists which is serving the community of collectors / investors. Tere are&#xA;options from companies from my child-hood who are stuck in the past. There are&#xA;options from hobbyist who haven&amp;rsquo;t created a serious offering. Finally, there are&#xA;markets that don&amp;rsquo;t cater to the sports fans (Ebay.) Much activity happens in the&#xA;walled gardens of Facebook, and that&amp;rsquo;s a clear indicator of a market ready to be&#xA;served.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Going Nuclear</title>
      <link>/post/going-nuclear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/going-nuclear/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.zerohedge.com/energy/google-turns-nuclear-power-power-its-data-centers&#34;&gt;From Zerohedge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The big tech companies are betting on nuclear. This will be an interesting development to check into. It has always been difficult to cut through the noise of nuclear vs renewable. Renewable energy people high high conviction and they make a lot of noise. Nuclear has no such champions, until now. Money talks, and it&amp;rsquo;s talking to nuclear.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The greatest argument I see against nuclear is that it&amp;rsquo;s too expensive to compete with solar. However, cost of power isn&amp;rsquo;t as much of a concern when it&amp;rsquo;s standing between you and billions of dollars in investments into AI. I&amp;rsquo;m guessing this is a diversity play. The big tech players will take power wherever they can get it. And apparently they are finding some potentially easy pickings for nuclear.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello, you have found the playground of John Fuller. I use this site to post about things which I feel are interesting and potentially impactful to my life. This site isn&amp;rsquo;t about news or posting for the sake of posting. I&amp;rsquo;m not trying to be an influencer. There&amp;rsquo;s maybe a handful of people who might be interested in what I post here. I really feel the things I post here are part of a tapestry of things which could have a direct impact on me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
